As the curtain rises
on our verisimilitudinous tableau,
you're no doubt curious
as to why I tricked you all
into hang gliding here.
Close-up.
It seems someone in this room
is a murderer.
It's me.
But the real question is,
which of you is the victim?
And that secret I shall take to my grave.
Calculon, no!
Now, that's acting.
Calculon really Shatnered
the hell out of that scene.
Hey, anyone want to go to the aquarium?
They got a new non-biting otter.
- Sounds great!
- Non-biting otter!
Wow. Aquariums have really
changed since I was a boy
and no one ever took me to them.
Where's the glass?
There isn't any. The water's
held in place by gravity fields
so there's nothing
for kids to smear yogurt on.
I like strawberry yogurt.
Can I touch the water?
I wouldn't, but I'm smart.
Ahhh!
Help. Police.
Neat.
Welcome to Jurassic Tank.
Picture time.
Everybody get together.
Hang on, I need a tripod.
Let me just extend the old third leg.
Ooh, yeah. That's stable, baby.
Just need to pick a lens.
Let's see, zoom lens?
Nope.
They Live lens?
Eh... So-so.
Twilight Zone
one-minute-in-the-future lens?
Ooh, Calculon's going to be here.
Better get my camera ready.
Just take the damn picture.
Let me just adjust the focus,
F-stop, shutter speed.
Oops! Out of film. Hang on.
Seriously.
Film? Who uses film?
We've had digital cameras
for a thousand years.
Digital?
No digital camera can capture
the warmth and grain of good old film.
How can you even tell?
Your eyes are digital cameras.
And where can you possibly
get film developed nowadays?
Right here.
You're looking at
the last chemical darkroom in existence.
Hey, Bender,
isn't that Calculon?
Calculon? No way!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Yo, Calky!
I'm a big fan, and I've got a big camera.
Can I get a big picture?
Well, I was just airbrushed this morning,
so all right.
But make it snappy.
That looked staged.
Try one where you're pretending
to swing a tennis racquet.
Okay, okay, that's enough.
I'm trying to enjoy a nice day out
with the actors who play my TV family.
These rare and fascinating deep-sea fish
are extremely sensitive to light.
Over here, Calculon!
Come on, smile. Quit blinking. Red eye.
Blurry. Lens cap's still on.
Oh! We finally eluded
that obnoxious shutterbug.
At last, we can enjoy
our studio-mandated quality time.
Argh! I can't not work like this.
I'll be in my day-off trailer.
And I took this one inside
the ichthyosaur's stomach.
Man, I've never had
anyone try so hard to digest me.
Look, we've all been
in a sea monster's stomach.
But did you get any pictures
of the Calculon?
Yeah, but a true photo buff
wouldn't even use these for toilet paper.
Not if curtains were available.
You're too hard on yourself, robot.
These pictures are just as good
as the ones in my celebrity tabloid.
Us People Magazine?
That's total trash.
Total celebrity trash.
My inquiring organ wants to know.
If you ask me,
Bender should go
to Us People's office in Hollywood
and see if they'd like
his Calculon pictures.
I have no time for such foolishness.
Well, I changed my mind and
came to Hollywood after all.
Bender, these shots of Calculon are great.
In fact, you might
just have what it takes to be a paparazzo.
Namely, a camera.
Shut up. I know it.
Wait, a what's-a-whatzo?
A paparazzo.
You know, a celebrity photographer.
But it's not for everyone.
You'd have to wallow in Hollywood filth,
loiter in dark alleys
behind seedy nightclubs
and get spat on by the beautiful people.
Hmm, I don't know.
How much will it cost me?
You misunderstand, Bender.
We'll pay you.
Sir, you just hired yourself
a new what's-a-whatzo.
Listen up, gang,
I'd like to introduce you to Bender,
the newest member
of our paparazzo family.
Nice to meet you.
And even though it's only my first day,
I want you all to know
that I'm already better than you.
Stay out of my way!
I'm back, Crab Dip.
What you watching?
Only a documentary
about the greatest actor in the world.
Ah, yes, Calculon.
I happened to snap a picture of him
taking some time with his biggest fan.
No, not that scene-chewing ham.
I said the greatest actor,
Langdon Cobb. Let's rewind, shall we?
Langdon Cobb, the most
acclaimed actor of his generation.
Why's he wearing a bag on his head?
They're explaining that right now.
Let's rewind again.
...most acclaimed
actor of his generation.
He's raked in seven Academy Awards
for best actor
and two for best actress,
all without ever removing
his trademark bag.
Mr. Cobb, you're an intensely private man.
Quite right.
Mmm-hmm.
And though billions of people
have seen your work...
- Mmm-hmm.
- ...no one has ever seen your face.
So tell us, why the bag?
Ah, yes, the bag. I've never understood
people's fascination with that.
The point is, I'm an actor
and nothing more.
I have no interest in being admired
for something as inconsequential
as my appearance or my personal life.
All that truly matters is the process.
Whether playing
a beloved historical figure.
For Rigel 7 and all mankind!
Or a Victorian circus freak...
I want to see the real you.
No, Daisy, don't!
I tried to warn you.
I'm hideous.
To me, you're beautiful.
...Langdon Cobb's
acting is always in the bag.
Truly, his is the most
famous face in Hollywood.
Even if no one's ever photographed it,
nor ever will.
Once again,
television has given me a reason to live.
A photo of Langdon Cobb
without his bag? Impossible.
He's got a 50-foot-high force field
around his house.
One 60-foot ladder, please.
Oh!
What are you, some kind of attack fungus?
Or just a moldy schnauzer?
Oh, God,
please let this tacky Hollywood mansion
have the obligatory...
Yes! Tuscan-inspired pergola!
Peace out, Portobello.
Thank you, Leroy.
I'm going to relax by the fire
with my bag off,
so that will be all for the night.
By your command.
Come to paparazzo.
- Gotcha!
- No!
Please, sir, I implore you,
destroy that photo of me.
It's not just my privacy
I've been protecting all these years.
If you show anyone that picture,
there will be terrible consequences.
The only thing terrible is
going to be my bank account.
Wait. Say that again, but say,
"Tremendous consequences."
If it's money you're after,
I'll pay whatever you ask.
Just promise me
you'll never show that photo to anyone.
I swear on my honor as a paparazzo.
Hey, Fry, want to see a picture?
Sure.
Hmm... He looked at the photo
and that happened.
But it could just be a coincidence.
Yo, Amy, check it out.
The evidence is mounting.
Although two times
hardly establishes a pattern.
I'd feel more comfortable
raising the alarm
if I were a little more certain.
Hey, how'd those two get deflated?
They looked at this.
That proves it.
Looking at this photo of Langdon Cobb
has a horrific effect on living creatures.
Hey, Zoidberg,
look at this photo of Langdon Cobb.
What, a picture of Langdon Cobb?
Now, this I want to see
as clearly as possible.
Zoidberg, no!
Oh, thank God, Professor.
You got here just in time.
I've seen this before.
Langdon Cobb must be from Bryoria Six,
home of the quantum lichen people.
Well, that explains that.
They're attention parasites.
They feed on the admiration of their prey.
Just like the noble buffalo.
Nothing like a buffalo.
Anyone who pays attention to the lichen
is unknowingly feeding it.
But gaze upon its face,
even in a photograph,
and your very life force will be
sucked out, leaving you a flaccid husk.
So the picture robbed them of their souls?
Souls? Don't be ridiculous. It's their
life forces that have been stolen.
It's scientific.
That's why the robot's immune.
He has no soul.
Life force!
So, how do we get their life forces back?
If we poke a hole in Cobb's bag,
will they spew out like a volcano
built on an Indian graveyard?
Alas, it's not that simple.
You see, just as the Earth lichen
is composed of an algae and a fungus,
the quantum variety
is also composed of two separate parts.
An attractive algae-based id
and a ravenous fungus-based ego
that stores the stolen souls.
I mean, life forces.
Now, here's the weird part.
The ego and the id are connected
not physically,
like decent, God-fearing Earth lichens,
but by quantum entanglement.
So the id is Langdon Cobb,
but this fungus ego could be...
Anywhere!
We'll never find it.
Let's just give up and
go to the aquarium again.
Now, hold on. I feel like
I was chased by a mushroom recently.
Of course!
The guard dog at Cobb's estate.
That's the ego.
All right, let's go.
It'll be just like stomping a puppy.
No, no, no.
Subduing an actor's ego is no easy task.
We'll have to weaken it first.
Look, I own words that are helpful.
It says the World Acting Championship
is tonight in Hollywood.
Quiet, Zoidberg.
God, I wish you were a husk.
No, it's Langdon Cobb versus Calculon.
If we help Calculon win,
it will weaken Cobb's ego, maybe?
Yes, yes, fine.
We never go
where I want to go.
So, the most galling of the paparazzi
needs my help.
Lo, the worm has turned.
Say cheese, Calculon without makeup.
As much as I hate you,
I hate Langdon Cobb more.
He beats me out for every award,
every role, every paternity suit.
Besting him at acting
means more to me than life itself.
And we want to help you.
Now, your only chance
is a classic death scene.
One with a lot of "thy's" and "thou's."
Voilà. The tragic end of
Rome O. and Julie T.
That's Romeo and Juliet,
dummy, by Will.i.am Shakespeare.
Now, here's the poison
that Romeo uses to kill himself.
Don't worry, it's just water
and food coloring.
Food coloring?
The most poisonous substance
known to robots?
Oops! Sorry. I'll swap it out
for harmless battery acid.
No. Wait.
There's only one way to ensure victory.
I must perform the ultimate death scene.
I shall drink the actual poison
and actually die.
But, Calculon, you can't kill yourself.
I'm a celebrity.
I can kill anyone I want.
Call it in the air.
Comedy.
It's tragedy. Langdon Cobb
will be first to take the stage.
Bossy to Stinky.
Come in, Stinky.
I always come in stinky.
Stand by.
The competition's about to begin.
Oh!
Hold your fire until Calculon's
performanceweakens the ego.
Roger. Stinky over.
Whoof! I beg to differ.
I wish it had been me, Sully.
I wish it had been me off-duty
in the Garden
when those drug lords blew up the Celtics.
But I was drunk, wicked drunk.
Uh-oh. Cobb's doing a scene
from Beantown Buddies.
The audience is eating it up.
Professor, what's your status?
Not good.
The attention Cobb's receiving
is inflating his ego.
It's going totally Kanye.
Wow!
There's a humungous fungus among us.
Oh, Sully,
you were the best partner I ever had,
both on the beat
and in the sack.
That's right, I said it.
I said it.
A tough act to follow.
And now, to follow that act,
performing the death scene
from Romeo and Juliet,
seven-time Oscar runner-up, Calculon!
Ah, dear Juliet,
why art thou yet so fair?
I will stay with thee
and never from this
palace of dim night depart again.
Oh, here will I set up my everlasting rest
and shake the yoke of inauspicious stars
from this world-wearied flesh.
Eyes, look your last.
Arms, take your last embrace.
And lips, oh, you, the doors of breath,
seal with a righteous kiss.
Here's to my love.
I can't believe he really did it.
At least he died
knowing I was great.
Uh-oh.
That death scene
was almost half believable.
Cobb looks jealous and insecure.
How's his ego doing?
It's shrinking.
Faster, Professor, kill, kill.
Activating anti-fungal ray.
It just has to warm up
for about 15 minutes.
Ladies and gentlemen and smizmars,
we have a unanimous decision.
The winner and
Heavyweight Acting Champion of the world,
Langdon Cobb!
Huh.
Thank you. Thank you. Thanks.
Oh, God, he's basking in their admiration.
That ego must be at
least four feet tall by now.
Aw! Did you miss me, pookie?
- Ow!
- Oh!
I can't watch.
I better take some pictures.
Wait a minute.
When living creatures look
at Cobb's photo,
their life force gets sucked out.
And Cobb's a living creature.
I just need to show him
a picture of himself.
But I tore up the only picture of Cobb.
And everybody knows,
once you delete a photo,
it's gone forever.
Maybe a digital photo,
but with film, I still have the negative.
Hurry, make a new print.
I don't know
how long I can distract Cobb's ego.
Okay. I'll be in the darkroom.
Eh...
Contrast is a little off on this one.
Oh!
Bender, hurry up!
This one is really good.
But I can still do better.
Who are you people?
Why are you attacking my ego?
You stole our friends' life forces.
Ah, yes. I warned the robot,
but he wouldn't listen.
You see, I was once
like the rest of my species,
showing my face to one planet,
draining its life force and moving on.
But when I got to Earth,
I found a different kind of prey.
Explain. Oh!
You Earthlings
worship celebrity with such fervor
that I can survive
simply by milking your admiration.
Milking and milking it
through what we actors call "the process."
Oh, God,
just kill us already.
But you all discovered my secret.
And for that, you will pay.
- Look at me!
- If we do,
will you stop talking about the process?
Never. Behold!
I'll save you, Leela,
Professor and Zoidberg.
Oops!
Nonetheless, I finally nailed it.
Gaze upon this photo of yourself
and start squirting out some soul-arrhea.
It doesn't work that way, you imbecile.
Although it's really
quite a nice portrait.
The contrast is exquisite.
And the composition sublime.
I look spectacular.
Aw, man. My great photo
only made his ego bigger.
No. No!
Oh!
Hey, Calculon's dead.
What happened?
Did you save us, Leela?
Actually, no.
For once, it was Bender.
Really? Well, thanks
for whatever you did, Bender.
It was a lot,
and you'll never be able to pay me back.
Now, gather round, friends,
so we can commemorate
this moment in a photo.
I got to admit,
this time, it'll be a pleasure
to be in your picture.
Say, "Bender is great."
Bender is great!
Neat.